Shayan Yousefian

Web Developer

Address – Birkdale Dr St. Catherines, ON



T +1 647 863 1891 info@shayanys.com

About Me



Software developer with more than 5 years of experience in web-based startups. Fast learner, with conceptual thinking. Good taste in art and design, piano player and photography enthusiast. My passion is to be a game developer and an entrepreneur. In general, I love creating new things, that's why I became a software developer.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Full Stack Developer, Yektanet

Tehran, Iran — 2016-2018

Django (Python), REST APIs, Laravel (PHP), Wordpress (Plug-in and Theme development and maintenance)

Accomplishments:

- Creating an inovative and successful advertisement platform named, Yektanet.com.
- High-Performance web-service and database design.

PHP Developer, Bamilo



Tehran, Iran — 2015-2016

Laravel (PHP), Live transactions for e-mail marketing and data-processing migrations for business, Telegram Bot for marketing.

Accomplishments:

- Tight deadlines, International workplace.
- Creating inter-connection between different platforms using crawling and queries.

Junior Full Stack Developer, Pordo

Tehran, Iran — 2013-2015

Codeigniter (PHP), Multi-purpose CMS development and static page designs.

Accomplishments:

- Creating fully-customized CMS.
- Front-End development for dozens of websites.

SKILLS



COLLABORATIVE FAST LEARNER DRIVEN TO DELIVER CREATIVE
DISCRETE AND ETHICAL
MULTI TASKING

EDUCATION

Computer Science – Post-Graduate

Brock University, Ontario, Canada — 2017-2018 (expected, end of year)

Currently working on "Autogenerating quests for Role-Playing-Games" as my Master Project under the supervision of professor Michael Winter.



Computer Engineering – Under-Graduate

Shahid Beheshti, Tehran, Iran — 2012-2017

Dynamic server optimizer application as Bachelor's Project, GPA: 3.67 (major courses).

Physics and Mathematics – High School

Allameh-Helli, Tehran, Iran — 2008-2012

In this special school for talented students, I completed all the credits and got A⁺ grade overall.

C

LANGUAGES

English: fluent (TOEFL: 100) Persian: native language

HONORS - AWARDS

Admitted to State University (Shahid Beheshti, Tehran)



National Universities Entrance Exam (Concours) —2012 Ranked 1500 from 1.66 millions contestants.

Admitted to Exceptional Talents School

National Organization for Development of Exceptional Talents — 2005 & 2008

Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exerc. Irure dolor in reprehend incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua.